mooviees.com 2006-11-17

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Why do we offer a Privacy Policy?**   
This Privacy Policy has been created by MoovieesNetwork, the operators of the Mooviees.com website, in an effort to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy on our site. 

Users can access and participate in all aspects of the Mooviees.com site without registering. Any information that we collect is designed to help us provide you with a more personalized experience. 

**What Information is Collected and Why?**   
Mooviees.com uses visitors' Internet Protocol (IP) addresses in order to help diagnose any problems with our server and for general administration of our web site. This IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

This site contains links to other sites and Mooviees.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to carefully review the policies of each respective site individually. 

Our site utilizes cookies, which (if you enable them in your browser) store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best and will save your moniker or email address so that you don't have to re-type it every time you post to our "Forum" boards. However, cookies reveal nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information. 

We also utilize an outside advertising company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other portions of our web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected independently by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**What About the Discussion Boards?**   
Mooviees.com offers access to our "Forum" boards for visitors. In order to post a message, users are required to provide an email address and their IP addresses are recorded. This is designed to protect the integrity of the board and dissuade participants from harassing or "flaming" others. 

Please remember that any information that is posted to this area becomes public information. Consequently, you should exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose any personal information. 

**Is all of this Information Secure?**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How do we deal with Third Parties?**   
Absolutely under no circumstances will Mooviees.com offer any personal information about you to somebody outside of our company without obtaining your prior consent. 

From time to time, we may provide aggregated statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information about you. 

**COPPA Compliance**   
Mooviees.com is prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary. In addition, a parent can review and have deleted the child's personal information, and refuse to permit further collection or use of the child's information. 

**Privacy Questions?**   
If you have any unanswered questions about our privacy statement or related dealings with our site, please contact us at: 

Mooviees.com  
72 Tory Square   
Waterville   
Blanchardstown   
Dublin 15
